{}《绝望主妇》前情提要
Previously on Desperate Housewives
{}你雇用我到底要做什么
Exactly what is it that you hired me to do?
{}有人把那张字条寄给我妻子
Someone sent that note to my wife.
{}我想知道是谁
I need to know who.
{}一些秘密被发现
Some secrets were discovered.
{}我妈妈去世之后
After mom died,
{}我开始回忆起发生在丹娜身上的事
I started remembering what happened to Dana.
{}丹娜是谁
Who's Dana?
{}你在这儿干吗
What are you doing here?
{}另一些秘密被揭开
Some secrets were uncovered.
{}她可能跟这里的任何一个男人有染
It could be anyone of these guys she's having an affair with.
{}别担心 她逃不出我的法眼
Don't worry. I'm not letting her out of my sight.
{}还有一些秘密...
And some secrets...
{}乔丹娜·盖斯特就能完成任务
Jordana Geist managed to get her work done.
{}你怎么能干这么多活
How do you cram it all in?
{}被分享
...were shared.
{}这药是治注意力缺乏症的
That's ADD medication.
{}竞争 通常因人而异
Competition. It means different things to different people.
{}在郊区 竞争意味着跟上邻居的脚步
In suburbia, it means keeping up with the Joneses.
{}在紫藤郡 那就意味着
On Wisteria Lane, that means
{}向布里·范德坎普看齐
keeping up with Bree Van de Kamp.
{}众所周知布里拥有紫藤郡最美的草坪
Everyone knew Bree had the nicest lawn in the neighborhood.
{}没有人嫉妒她这点
And no one begrudged her this.
{}除了玛莎·胡博
No one, that is, except Martha Huber,
{}和布里相比 她家的草坪就稍显逊色
whose own lawn paled in comparison.
{}无论她如何仔细修剪
No matter how carefully she trimmed,
{}辛勤灌溉
or how lovingly she watered...
{}抑或是毫不吝啬地施肥
or how generously she fertilized,
{}篱笆那头的草坪还是比她的要绿一些
the grass was always greener on the other side of the fence.
{}维克多 你好吗
Hello, Victor. How are you today?
{}-又去跑步了 -我 透不过气了
- Out jogging again? - I can't... catch my breath.
{}要不要就着我的水管喝点水
Would you like a slurp from my hose?
{}维克多
Victor?
{}别怕 我这去叫救护车
Don't worry. I'm gonna get an ambulance.
{}这一天 胡博太太终于等到
Then one day, Mrs. Huber finally got
{}机会来打败对手
the chance to mow down the competition.
{}救命 有没有人啊
Help! Somebody help!
{}发生什么事了
What happened?
{}他昏倒在你的绣花球上 快打911
He collapsed on your hydrangeas. Call 911!
{}胡博太太明白竞争的第一守则
Yes, Mrs. Huber understood the first rule of competition
{}为了赢得胜利 你得伺机而动
In order to win, you have to want it more.
{}《绝望的主妇》第一季 第七集
Desperate Housewives S01E07
{}当我还在世的时候
When I was alive,
{}我和我的朋友每个月都会聚首于
my friends and I came together once a month
{}紫藤郡读书俱乐部的会议
for a meeting of the Wisteria Lane book club.
{}我们对书中的人物故事十分着迷
We found the problems of literary characters so absorbing.
{}包括他们面对困境的方式
The way they dealt with adversity,
{}处理不正当的婚外情
conducted illicit affairs,
{}忍受不断的家庭闹剧
endured domestic dramas,
{}对浪漫的无限憧憬
and planned romantic conquests.
{}但是自从我去世之后
But since my death,
{}我的朋友们对小说兴趣乏乏
my friends had lost their interest in fiction.
{}那么 大家是怎么想的
So, what did everybody think?
{}他们自己的问题就足够他们头疼了
Their own problems had become absorbing enough.
{}我觉得包法利夫人这个人物
I thought the character of Madame Bovary
{}非常鼓舞人心
was very inspirational.
{}鼓舞人心 她服砒霜自杀了
Inspirational? She poisons herself with arsenic.
{}-真的吗 -你没有读完吗
- Really? - You didn't read until the end?
{}我只读到第50页
I stopped after page 50.
{}难道只有我一个人读完整本书吗
Am I the only one who read the book?
{}我看过电影 很不错
I saw the movie. It was really good.
{}女士们 我很遗憾
Ladies, I'm sorry,
{}可如果大家都不看书
but what is the point of having a book club
{}那这个读书俱乐部还有什么意义呢
if we don't read the book?
{}再来点酒吗
More wine?
{}苏 瑞芭 艾玛和洛丽
Sue, Reba, Emma and Lori,
{}你们能否到厨房帮我准备下点心
would you girls come and help me with the snacks?
{}好的
Sure.
{}我马上就来
I will be right in.
{}天哪 我想立刻就甩掉她们
God, I couldn't wait to get rid of them!
{}勒奈特说你找到扎克了
Ok, so Lynette said that you found Zach.
{}他在康复中心
He's at a rehabilitation center.
{}朱莉偷溜进去还和他说话了
Julie snuck in and actually talked to him.
{}他有没有说什么关于他母亲自杀的事
Did he say anything about his mother's suicide?
{}没那么多时间
There wasn't enough time.
{}但他的确说了一件很神秘的事
But he did say one thing that was kind of mysterious.
{}他说在某个叫丹娜的人身上发生了些事
He said something happened to someone named Dana
{}他却永远不能提及此事
And that he could never ever talk about it.
{}-谁是丹娜 -这正是神秘之处
- Who the hell is Dana? - That's the mystery part.
{}我认为这个丹娜和玛丽·艾莉丝
I figure Dana has something to do with
{}所隐瞒的事有一定的关联
what Mary Alice was trying to hide.
{}所以有人发现了玛丽·艾莉丝的秘密
So somebody found out Mary Alice's secret...
{}-然后寄了字条 -究竟会是谁呢
- And sent the note. - So who the hell is that?
{}这张纸是帕彻17号的 纯棉
Stationery is Parcher no.17. 100% cotton.
{}是塞普勒斯文具用品公司的产品
It's made by Cyprus Office products.
{}他们在12家城市有专卖店
They have stores in 12 cities,
{}包括你所在的城市
including yours.
{}我们发现邮戳来自你们本地的邮局
We traced that postmark back to your local post office.
{}所以呢
Meaning?
{}就是说你很可能认识这个勒索者
Meaning is that the blackmailer's probably someone you know.
{}邻居 送奶工
A neighbor, milkman,
{}泳池小弟 爱心妈妈
pool boy, soccer mom.
{}爱心妈妈
Soccer mom?
{}杨先生 魔鬼有时还开着小货车呢
Mr. Young, sometimes evil drives a minivan.
{}曾经有个案例
I had this gig once,
{}一个家庭教师协会的家长
checking on this PTA mom
{}不惜一切想为她的女儿
who was hell-bent on landing her daughter
{}赢得参加花车巡游的席位
a spot on the parade float.
{}她给一半的学生代表吃了防冻剂
She fed antifreeze to half the homecoming committee.
{}-你没有抓到她吗 -杨先生
- Did you catch her? - Mr. Young...
{}雇佣我的人并非要我抓她
The people who hired me didn't hire me to catch her.
{}亲爱的 咱们家简直一尘不染
Wow, honey! This place is spotless.
{}多谢
Thanks.
{}我已经为这次的洁力强广告
So Listen, I have come up with this
{}想出一个绝妙的主意
killer idea for the spotless scrub campaign.
{}太好了 要我帮你参谋参谋吗
Great. Want to run it by me?
{}不用了
No. I'm good.
{}-多谢夫人关心 -好的
- But thanks. - Oh. Ok.
{}是这样的 你知道每次我的想法
Well that's the thing... you know how whenever I pitch
{}总是被亨尼斯在合伙人面前贬得一文不值
Hennessey always tears my ideas down in front of the partners?
{}是吗
Yeah?
{}所以我邀请了合伙人夫妇到家里来
I invited the partners and their wives over
{}这样我就能好好阐明我的理念
so I could pitch to them here.
{}我们可以举办个正式的六人晚餐
I thought we could make a formal dinner for six...
{}可以坐着 也可以...
We can sit, we can...
{}具体是什么时间呢
When exactly would this formal dinner take place?
{}-后天 -汤姆
- Ah, the day after tomorrow. - Tom!
{}-我知道这太仓促了 -你说呢
- I know it's short notice. - You think?
{}突然让我办个正式晚餐 我怎么做得到
How am I supposed to pull off a formal dinner with no warning?
{}我哪知道
I don't know.
{}布里·范德坎普就常做这样的事
Bree Van de Kamp does this kind of thing all the time.
{}你说什么
What did you say?
{}对不起 我没那个意思
I'm sorry. I didn't mean it like that.
{}算了 我去打电话取消
You know what. Forget it. I'll call and cancel.
{}别担心了
Just don't worry about it.
{}不要 我们办吧
No. No, let's do it.
{}真的吗
Really?
{}真的 这关系到你的升迁
Yeah. It's good for your career.
{}我一定尽力办好
I'll pull it off.
{}太好了 亲爱的 太谢谢你了
Yes! Honey, thank you so much.
{}我保证一旦我搞定这笔买卖
You know what. I promise, I land this account
{}我就给你买个超漂亮的礼物
and I am gonna buy you something awful pretty.
{}汤姆是幸运的 勒奈特有成功的秘籍
Luckily for Tom, Lynette had a recipe for success.
{}不幸的是 秘籍少了必备配料
Unfortunately for her, she was missing the secret ingredient.
{}-你好 -是我
- Yeah. - It's me.
{}别转身 我婆婆能看见你
Don't turn around! My mother-in-law can see you.
{}我讨厌她一直盯着我们
I hate that she's watching us.
{}那一个小时后旅馆见
So meet me at the motel in an hour.
{}-约翰 -我有其他事
- John? - Uh... I've got plans.
{}取消不就行了
So cancel.
{}是丹妮尔 我们要去看电影
They're with Danielle. We're going to the movies.
{}-听起来像是约会 -没错
- That sounds like a date. - Yeah.
{}我不喜欢你去见其他女孩
Well, I have a problem with you seeing other girls.
{}我还不喜欢你有老公呢
I have a problem with you having a husband.
{}我们都得学着面对
I guess we both have to learn to deal.
{}别以为挑逗我就能补偿我
Don't even try to make it up to me by talking dirty.
{}喂
Hello?
{}范德坎普先生 太太
Mr. and Mrs. Van de Kamp.
{}你们的儿子昨天为了
So, your son decided to
{}取乐他的几个朋友
entertain some of his friends yesterday
{}把一个新生的头推进寄物柜里
by shoving a freshman's head into a locker.
{}就是詹森家的孩子吗
This was the Johnson boy?
{}是的 他把那孩子的鼻子弄断了
Yes. He broke the boy's nose.
{}因为我们向来治学严谨
Because of our no tolerance policy,
{}你的儿子可能要退学
your son may face expulsion.
{}因为小打小闹就要毁掉他的未来吗
You're gonna ruin his future over roughhousing?
{}雷克斯 这快构成伤害罪了
Rex, this was practically assault.
{}斯塔克老师 安德鲁确实做错了
Mrs. Stark, what Andrew did was clearly wrong.
{}不过在他的立场上 我和他母亲
But in his defence, his mother and I are going
{}正遭遇严重的婚姻问题
through severe marital problems.
{}和这有关系吗
Is that relevant?
{}我们的婚姻就快支离破碎了
Our marriage is disintegrating.
{}他当然需要发泄 他有权愤怒
Of course Andrew is acting out. He has every right to be angry.
{}如果他是因为你搬出去而愤怒
If he's angry about you moving out the house,
{}那他应该把你的头推进寄物柜里
perhaps he should shove your head into a locker.
{}我只是说 我们也有责任
All I'm saying is we need to take some of the responsibility here.
{}有责任的是安德鲁 把他的行为归罪到
So does Andrew. Blaming his actions on our problems,
{}我们的小问题上 这对他没好处
which are not serious, does not help him.
{}我们的问题很严重
Our problems are serious.
{}斯塔克老师 你按规矩处理吧
Mrs. Stark, you handle this however you see fit.
{}布里 我见过律师了
Bree, I've gone to an attorney.
{}今天晚些时候你就会收到离婚协议书
You're gonna be served with divorce papers later today.
{}-你去见了律师 -是啊
- You went to an attorney? - Yeah.
{}而且是个很好的
And a good one, too.
{}他最好很能干 一旦我们离婚
He'd better be, 'cause when I'm finished with you,
{}你名下将不会有一分钱
you won't have a cent to your name.
{}尽管放马过来
Bring it on.
{}我们就罚他留校查看吧
Perhaps detention is the way to go.
{}妈妈 你打扮得太正式了
Mom, you're getting too dressed up.
{}我知道 可我想让自己看上去更性感
I know, but I wanna look really sexy.
{}我告诉朋友你会在11点回家
I told my guys perheps you have to go home by 11
{}12点怎么样
Hm. How about midnight?
{}好吧 但是不能再晚了
All right, but no later.
{}我会担心的 你采取保护措施了吗
You know how I worry. So, you got protection?
{}天哪 我们没必要谈论这个话题
Oh, my god! We are so not having this conversation.
{}有必要 因为我喜欢独生子的感觉
We are, because I enjoy being an only child.
{}-你说完了吗 -快了
- Are you finished? - Almost.
{}我一直觉得我的第一次
You know I always assumed I'd have sex for the first time
{}要比你的下一次来得早
before you had it again.
{}好了 你快走吧
Ok, you can leave now.
{}你觉得怎么样 是不是太刻意了
What do you think? Trying too hard?
{}你知道什么
What do you know?
{}外面有80度而你还穿着一身的毛
It's 80 degrees outside and you're wearing fur.
{}你好 麦克
Hi, Mike.
{}伊迪
Hey, Edie.
{}瞧瞧 你看上去太漂亮了
Wow! Get a load of you! You look so pretty!
{}-我差点认不出你 -这个吗
- I hardly recognize you. - Oh, this?
{}我和麦克有个约会
Well, I have a date. Right now. With Mike.
{}我们接吻了 仅供你参考
We kissed, F.Y.I.
{}外套不错 选得很好
Oh, love that jacket. Good choice.
{}苏珊 对不起我得取消约会
Um, Susan, I am really sorry, but I've got to cancel.
{}我有个突如其来的访客
I have an unexpected house guest.
{}进来吧 抱歉 我是凯德拉
Coming through. Ooh, sorry. Hi. I'm Kendra.
{}苏珊
Susan.
{}我去车上取点东西
I'm going to run to the car and get my stuff.
{}我知道这看起来很容易误会
I know how this looks,
{}但我们之间真的没有什么
but there's nothing between us.
{}-凯德拉只是个老朋友 -老朋友
- Kendra's just an old friend. - Old friend.
{}是的 你明白的
Yeah, you know...
{}没错... 不 其实我不明白
Yeah, yeah... No, actually, no, I don't know.
{}老朋友是指学校同学
By old friend you mean college pal?
{}保龄球友
Bowling buddy?
{}还是救命恩人
Saved you from drowning?
{}-这很难解释清楚 -就不能试试吗
- It's hard to explain. - Could you give it a shot?
{}麦克 我上楼去洗澡了
Mike, I'm gonna go upstairs and take a shower.
{}我保证一定会补偿你
Look, I promise I'll make this up to you.
{}-你看上去太惊艳了 -麦克 毛巾在哪
- And... You look amazing. - Mike! where are the towels?
{}多谢
Thanks.
{}你的约会怎么样
Hey. How was your big date?
{}麦克不得不改变时间
Mike had to reschedule.
{}因为那个辣妹吗
Oh. Because of the hot girl?
{}就那个带着箱子的
With the suitcase? Over there?
{}真为你感到遗憾 仅供你参考
Gosh, how devastating for you... F.Y.I.
{}我只想快点搬走
I just want to move this place fast.
{}我会完成所有该做的事
I'll do whatever we have to do.
{}正高兴你这么说
That's good to know.
{}你明白你必须说明
You do realize that you'll have to disclose the fact that
{}你妻子在房子里自杀的事实
your wife killed herself in the house.
{}-必须吗 -法律规定
- I am? - Oh, yeah. Legal crap.
{}人们会被自杀这事吓坏的
People get really freaked out by suicides.
{}你可不能责怪他们
You can't blame them.
{}上帝 光是站在这我都觉得害怕
Hell. I get the willies just standing here.
{}-有什么方法能掩饰吗 -非正式的
- Is there any way to get around it? - Off the record?
{}你可以说她在客厅自杀
You could say that she shot herself in the living room
{}接着爬到后院才去世的
and then crawled out back to die.
{}我只是说说
I'm just saying.
{}我得走了 明天给你打电话
Oh, I gotta go. I'll call you tomorrow.
{}伊迪 等等
Edie, wait!
{}保罗一直知道
Paul had always known
{}伊迪·布利特为达目的可以不择手段
Edie britt was capable of doing anything to close a deal.
{}而他今天才意识到她的手段无人能及
But now he realized she was capable of so much more.
{}-你好 丹妮尔 -你好 索利斯夫人
- Hey, Danielle. - Hey, Mrs. Solis.
{}丹妮尔
Oh, Danielle,
{}还记得你说想要当模特吗
remember when you said you wanted to be a model?
{}你还记得吗 去年夏天的事了
You remember? That was last summer.
{}帕奇克模特学校
Well, as it turns out, Perchik Modeling Academy
{}将在今年夏天开设暑期课程
has an opening for their summer program.
{}希望我推荐你去吗
Would you like me to sponsor you?
{}天哪 那是国家最好的学校之一啊
Oh my god. That's one of the best schools in the country.
{}-你真的愿意帮我吗 -当然
- You would do that for me? - I sure would.
{}纽约是我梦寐以求的地方
I would so love to go to New York.
{}我很高兴可以帮你达成梦想
Oh, and I would so love to help you get there.
{}-乔丹娜 -勒奈特 你好吗
- Hey, Jordana. - Hey, Lynette. How are you?
{}你看起来有点累 一切都好吗
You look a little tired. Is everything ok?
{}我正在为明天六人的小聚会做准备
I'm getting ready for a dinner party tomorrow. Six people.
{}-听上去不错 -很有趣 才怪
- Sounds fun. - Big fun.
{}那个治疗孩子多动症的药
You wouldn't have any of your kids'
{}你还有没有多余的
ADD medication you could spare,
{}来帮我挺过这一关
just to get me over the hump?
{}蒂娜 别推妹妹
Tina! Don't push your sister.
{}勒奈特 我的也快吃完了
Gosh, Lynette... I'm really running low.
{}我需要为自己储存精力
I need all my energy I can get.
{}我妹妹伊莲和她的孩子
My sister Elaine and her kids
{}要飞到城里玩一个礼拜
are flying into town for a week.
{}真好 我也希望我的妹妹可以经常来
That's exciting. I wish my sister would visit more often.
{}姐妹们是最棒的
Yeah, sisters are great.
{}三四片就行 我快挺不住了
Three or four pills. I'm hitting the wall.
{}平静下来的确很难受 可我爱莫能助
Yeah, the calm down can be a real bitch. I wish I could help.
{}我不会原谅你的
I'm not gonna forget about this, Jordana.
{}你这是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
{}孩子们聚会的时候 别带蒂娜来
Come girl scout cookie time, don't bring around little Tina
{}因为我们不在家
Because we won't be home.
{}这是要干什么
What's all this about?
{}你们都知道我和妈妈不合很久了
You know your mother and I have been unhappy for a while.
{}经过反躬自问
After a lot of soul-searching,
{}我们觉得离婚是最好的选择
we've decided that it would be better if we got divorced.
{}但是 无论我们之间是否有矛盾
But whatever problems your father and I may have,
{}永远都不影响我们爱你们这个事实
it doesn't change the fact that we love you very, very much.
{}-我有个问题 -说吧 尽管问
- I've got a question. - Go ahead. Ask whatever you want.
{}我能和爸爸一起住吗
Can I live with dad?
{}妈妈 我们必须面对它
Come on, mom, let's face it.
{}我们会把彼此逼疯的
We drive each other crazy.
{}丹妮尔 你也这么想吗
Danielle, is that what you'd prefer?
{}和你爸爸一起住
Danielle? To live with your father?
{}我无所谓 只要我有自己的卫生间就行
I don't really care, as long as I have my own bathroom.
{}这... 这酒
Um... All this, um... wine is,
{}让我觉得有点头疼
uh... giving me a... headache.
{}在这郊区待了6周 你就查了这么点
Six weeks in the suburban jungle, and this is all you got?
{}这一带有三百多个家庭
There are over 300 families in this subdivision.
{}逐个调查是很费时间的
It'll take time to check them all out.
{}爸爸说上次见面时 你打算退出
Dad said last time he saw you, you were ready to quit.
{}我改主意了
Now I changed my mind.
{}这是在浪费时间还有我爸的钱
This is a gigantic waste of your time and my father's money.
{}你怕这会花光你的遗产吗
Are you afraid he'll spend your inheritance?
{}这一点都不好笑
That's not funny.
{}-麦克 有件事 -什么
- Mike, here's the thing. - What?
{}爸爸不可能单独行动的
Dad can't chase ghosts alone.
{}如果你不干了 他也就没辙了
If you stop, he'll have to accept it's over.
{}我想要回以前的爸爸
Let me have my father back.
{}如果我退出了 他还会找其他人
If I quit he'll just hire somebody else.
{}你说这里没什么可查的就行了
Not if you tell him there's nothing here to find.
{}我不能那样做
I can't do that.
{}要是你女朋友发现
What happens when your girlfriend finds out
{}你不再是那个可爱的水管工会怎样
you're not just the sweet, neighborly plumber?
{}你这是在骗她 麦克
You're lying to her, Mike.
{}找到了
Oh, here it is.
{}太好了 这个能保持蟹肉的温度
Great. This'll keep the crab dip warm.
{}去掉螃蟹壳要花很久
It took forever to shell the little buggers,
{}但很值
But it'll be worth it.
{}你自己去螃蟹壳吗
You shelled your own crabs?
{}不是我多嘴
Okay, I don't want to butt in.
{}你太辛苦了吧 你看上去很疲惫
Are you doing too much? Cause you look exhausted.
{}我没事 喝点咖啡就行 谢啦
I'm fine. I just need some coffee. Thank you.
{}上帝啊 看这个刺绣
Oh, my god! Look at this embroidery!
{}"丹娜" 这个从哪儿来的
"Dana." Where did this come from?
{}保罗·杨的旧货大甩卖
Paul Young's garage sale.
{}丹娜
Dana.
{}丹娜是个宝宝
Dana was a baby.
{}喜欢吗
Surprise.
{}-不可能 -归你了 这是钥匙
- No way! - It's all yours. Here are the keys.
{}雷克斯 这是怎么回事
Rex, what's this about?
{}我小小破费了一笔
I went and splurged a little.
{}丹妮尔 这是你的
Oh, Danielle, here's your present.
{}-旅行箱 -没错
- Luggage? - Yeah.
{}为你去帕奇克模特学校准备的
It's to take with you to the Perchik Modeling Academy.
{}学费由我出
I'm footing the bill.
{}-你是说我可以去纽约吗 -等等
- You mean I can go to New York? - Wait a minute.
{}什么模特学校
What's this about a modeling academy?
{}是我的新职业 索利斯夫人会推荐我
It's my new career. Mrs. Solis is sponsoring me.
{}你怎么没告诉我
When were you planning on telling me?
{}她告诉我了 我觉得这主意不错
She told me, I think it's a great idea.
{}你们两个没看出来他的动机吗
Don't you two see what he's doing?
{}这是他的糖衣炮弹
He's trying to buy your love.
{}看在上帝的份上 别那么多疑
For god's sake. Don't be paranoid.
{}又是辆车又是模特学校的
A car? A modeling academy?
{}你应该先和我商量一下这些礼物的
You should have discussed these gifts with me first.
{}抱歉 孩子们 可我们不能接受
I'm sorry, kids. But we cannot accept them.
{}你不能听任她这样
You can't let her do this.
{}我们刚刚告诉孩子们离婚的事
Bree, we just told the kids we're getting divorced.
{}-现在宠宠他们又怎样 -我不同意
- Isn't it time to spoil them a little? - I said no.
{}他们也是我的孩子
You know what? They're my kids too,
{}我想给他们什么就给什么
and I can give them anything I want.
{}拿着吧
There you go.
{}-谢谢爸爸 -太好了
- Thank you, daddy. - Yes.
{}是不是你帮丹妮尔进的模特学校
Did you offer to help Danielle get into modeling school?
{}什么 是啊 也不是
What? Uh... Yes... No.
{}她是这么给你说的
Um... is that how she heard it?
{}是啊 加布丽尔 究竟是不是你推荐的
Yes. Gabrielle, did you or did you not offer to sponsor her?
{}我不过想帮个忙
I just wanted to help out.
{}那可是在纽约啊 上帝
It's in New York! For god sakes
{}你是怎么想的
Why would you suggest that?
{}那是她的梦想 你难道不希望她开心吗
It's her dream. Don't you want her to be happy?
{}不 而且我希望你将来能
No. And in the future I would appreciate you keeping
{}自己保留你那可笑的想法
your ridiculous ideas to yourself.
{}布里
Bree!
{}约翰
John.
John!
{}你太嫉妒丹尼尔了
You're so jealous of Danielle.
{}甚至要把她弄到纽约去
You tried to ship her off to New York?
{}我才不嫉妒 只是不喜欢分享罢了
I'm not jealous. I just don't like to share.
{}好吧 我不干了
Well, you know what? I quit.
{}园丁 我们 所有的
The yard. Us. Everything.
{}别这么意气用事
Oh, don't be that way.
{}要是我们不能在一起还有什么意义
What's the point, if we can never be together?
{}这一个小时 那一个小时
You know, an hour here, an hour there.
{}我不希望我们不欢而散
I don't want us to end on a bad note.
{}卡洛斯今晚有个宴会 我能溜出来
Carlos has this black tie thing tonight and I could slip out...
{}-索利斯夫人 -约翰 别这样
- Mrs. Solis! - John, please.
{}我们俩的一切是那么不同
What we had was so special.
{}总得有个像样的告别
I think it deserves a proper goodbye.
{}我们 我们还是会分手的
We'd, um... we'd still be over, though.
{}当然
Of course.
{}我就知道这个玩乐日的想法不错
I knew this play day was a good idea.
{}是啊 谢谢你的建议
Oh, yeah. Thank you for suggesting it.
{}只有你的孩子能让蒂米精疲力尽
Your boys are the only ones I know who could tire out Timmy.
{}是啊 他的确很调皮
Yep, he's a feisty one.
{}有传闻说 你在给蒂米药物治疗
Word on the street is, um, you've been medicating Timmy?
{}是啊 为了治他的多动症
Oh, yeah. For his ADD.
{}-简直是灵丹妙药 -我相信
- The pills have been a godsend. - I bet.
{}我能用下洗手间吗
Can I use your bathroom?
{}当勒奈特吞下那些偷来的
As Lynette swallowed the stolen
{}给八岁小孩吃的药的时候
medication of an eight-year-old child.
{}她发誓不能继续陷下去
She vowed she'd never again sink to such depths
{}短期内
any time soon.
{}看来找到敲诈你的人啦
Looks like you've got your blackmailer.
{}是不是该让警察介入了
Is it time to bring in the police?
{}这不在我的考虑范围内
That's not really an option for me.
{}我妻子自杀之前
Before my wife shot herself,
{}我很满足我们的生活
we lived a life that I was proud of.
{}深爱对方 有共同信仰
We loved each other. We had values.
{}一起去教堂 一起做慈善
We went to church. We gave to charity.
{}我们都是好人 肖先生
We were good people, Mr. Shaw.
{}我相信你
Oh, I believe you.
{}所以我很难理解为什么
That's why it's so incomprehensible to me that
{}伊迪·布利特这样破坏我们的家庭
Edie Britt would try to destroy us.
{}你失去的太多了
Well, you've suffered a great loss.
{}需要点时间来恢复
For your pain to heal, that's gonna take some time.
{}我等不及了
I can't wait.
{}我现在就急需帮助
I need help now.
{}我会让她加倍偿还的
For five grand she's hurt, ten grand she's gone.
{}妈 这是干什么
Mom, what's going on?
{}我要把你们都赶出去
Oh, I'm throwing you out.
{}我已经把你俩的东西分开放两边了
I've separated all your things into two sides.
{}这边是你的 丹妮尔
This side is yours, Danielle,
{}那边是安德鲁的
and the other one is Andrew's.
{}-好吧 你疯了 -你要我们去哪住
- Ok, you've lost it. - Where are we supposed to live?
{}亲爱的 我要知道就好了
Darling, if I know.
{}丹妮尔 北边那块
Danielle, everything in the north quadrant
{}全是衣服和书之类的
of your side is clothes and books and such.
{}南边就是些杂物
The south side are miscellaneous items.
{}妈 这样没用 我不会放弃我的车的
Mom, this isn't gonna work. I'm not giving up my car.
{}真明智 因为你可能得
That's smart. Because you'll probably gonna
{}在里面睡一阵了
have to sleep in it for a while.
{}妈 你阻止不了我们回屋
Mom, you can't stop us from going back inside the house.
{}是吗 那是锁匠 柯林先生
No? That's Mr. Conlin, the locksmith.
{}他今天可帮了不少忙
He's been very helpful today.
{}当然只要能做到我的条件
Of couse I could give you the new keys
{}我就给你们新钥匙
if you'd adhere to my rules,
{}包括把礼物还给你们的父亲
Which include giving back your father's gifts.
{}好吧 你赢了 我不去纽约了
Ok, fine. You win. I won't go to New York.
{}我走了
I'm outta here.
{}请进 我叫伊迪 初次见面
Oh, hello. Welcome. I'm Edie. How do you do?
{}郊外露天家庭聚会 真有创意
An open house in the suburbs? This is beyond kitsch.
{}别乱来
Just behavior yourself.
{}我可废了半天劲
This is one of the houses in the street
{}才能进这房子的
I've had a hard time getting into.
{}天啊 我正希望你能忘了这事
God, I wish you would let this go.
{}我今晚带你出去喝一杯
I'm taking you out for drinks tonight.
{}有个叫马鞍牧场的牛仔吧 你得看看
There's this cowboy bar called Saddle Ranch, you need to see.
{}为什么
Why?
{}那是你姐姐最后去过的地方
It's the last place anybody ever saw your sister.
{}苏珊 你怎么来了
Susan. What brings you here?
{}我是来和玛丽·艾莉丝的房子告别的
I just wanted to say goodbye to Mary Alice's house
{}在别人搬进来之前
before somebody else moved in.
{}真会花言巧语
That sounds almost plausible.
{}-什么 -拜托
- I beg your pardon? - Oh, come on.
{}我们都知道你为什么来这
We both know why you're here.
{}没错 他们肯定有一腿
And the answer is yes, they are having sex. No question.
{}你在说什么啊 他们不过是朋友
You know what you are talking about, they're just friends.
{}你真这么想吗
Hm. Think so?
{}我听到他们说今晚要去马鞍牧场
I over heared they say they're going to the Saddle Ranch tonight,
{}喝喝酒 跳跳舞
for drinks and dancing.
{}朋友们也会做这些的
Still, friends can do that.
{}上帝 我真想抽你一巴掌
Oh, my god, I just want to slap and shake you.
{}你刚说他们今晚要去哪
Where did you say they were going tonight?
{}我真不知道自己怎么就跟着你来了
I don't know why I let you talk me into coming here?
{}他俩明显不是那关系
There is obviously nothing going on between them.
{}你要去哪
Where are you going?
{}先去厕所然后回家
I'm going to the bathroom and then I'm going home.
{}我不想让麦克发现我在这
I don't want Mike to catch me here.
{}不过才十分钟
It's only been ten minutes.
{}她可能正要出手呢
She could be waiting to make her move.
{}临阵脱逃可打不败
Oh, come on. You're not gonna beat a girl like that
{}她这样的女孩
by knocking off early.
{}-这又不是比赛 -难道不是吗
- It's not a competition. - The hell it isn't.
{}晚安 伊迪
Good night, Edie.
{}随便你 但是提醒你
Suit yourself. But for the record...
{}我宁愿支持你拿下他
I was rooting for you to land him.
{}你为什么要支持我
And why would you root for me?
{}我觉得从你手里把麦克抢过来
I figured it'd be easier for me
{}可比从她手里轻松多了
to steal Mike from you than her.
{}她看起来挺精怪的
She seems like fun.
{}-吃点解酸药 -不是那种疼
- Just take some antacid. - It's not those kind of cramps.
{}这是商务晚餐 非常重要
This is a business dinner. It's important.
{}放松
Relax.
{}我们两个去吧
You and I can go alone.
{}让加布丽尔在这休息吧
Gabrielle can stay here and get better.
{}-好吧 过会见 -好
- Fine. See you in a couple of hours. - Ok.
{}-照顾好卡洛斯 -我一贯如此
- Take good care of Carlos. - Oh, I always do.
{}加油 伊迪
Go, Edie!
{}上帝啊
Oh, god.
{}麦克
Mike!
{}世界真小啊
What a small, small world.
{}是啊 我发现伊躲在后面
Yeah, it sure is. I caught Edie hiding in the back.
{}没开玩笑吧 她在这吗
No kidding. Is she here?
{}是啊 她说 开始摇吧
Yeah. Yeah, she said, "the jig is up,"
{}然后她就去骑牛了
and then she went to ride the bull.
{}-她还说你们一起来的 -是啊
- And she said you two came together. - Oh, well, yeah.
{}我们是一起来的 可我以为她走了
We did. I just thought she left.
{}-你在跟踪我吗 -什么
- Were you following me? - What?
{}当然不是 我只是和伊迪一起来这玩
No! No, I just came here, you know, with Edie.
{}我们爱骑牛
We just love to ride that bull.
{}-你也会骑牛 -是啊 突发奇想的
- You? Ride the bull? - Yeah. Yeah, it's a real rush.
{}得了 苏珊 饶了我吧
Come on, Susan. Give me a break.
{}是你饶了我吧 我没有跟踪你
You give me a break. I did not follow you here.
{}就算是 也不过因为
Even if I had followed you here, it's just because
{}你一直没提过凯德拉
you've been secretive about Kendra.
{}凯德拉和我是朋友
Kendra and I are friends.
{}而我是来骑牛的
And I came here to ride the bull.
{}我们找到下个骑牛者了
Whoo! We got another one to ride the bull!
{}小狗狗 到你啦
Ok, little doggie, you're up.
{}好吧 我是小狗狗
Oh, fine. I'm a doggie.
{}我就是来骑牛的
Oh, yeah. I'm here to ride this bull.
{}看着吧
Check it out. Whoo!
{}宝贝
Baby! whoo!
{}安德鲁 你答应和你妈妈住
Andrew, you promised you'd stay with your mother
{}我才给你车的
that's why I gave you the car.
{}爸 是她让我搬出来的
Dad, she wants me out.
{}她把我的东西都扔到草坪上了
She put all my stuff on the front lawn.
{}真可笑
This is ridiculous.
{}我要给她打电话解决这事
I'm gonna call her and smooth all this out.
{}-你得回家 -爸爸 别
- You're going home. - No, dad.
{}干吗
Why?
{}现在我能毫无负担的和你住啦
Now I can live with you without feeling guilty.
{}我们能相处好的 就像单身公寓一样
We'll be perfect. It'll be like our own little bachelor pad.
{}-怎么样 -儿子 这不可能
- What? - Son, that's not gonna happen.
{}-怎么不行 -安德鲁
- Why not? - Andrew...
{}这几月我过得很艰苦
These last few months have been incredibly difficult for me.
{}还有好多自己的事没解决
There are things I've got to work out for myself
{}要是和你一起住我什么也做不了 抱歉
and I can't do it if you're living with me. I'm sorry.
{}我不管 我不回去
I don't care. I'm not going back there.
{}-这不是你能决定的 -但是 爸
- I don't think you have a choice. - But, Dad...
{}听话 别这样
Oh, Come on now. Don't...
{}希勒 是我
Heath? Yeah, it's me.
{}你的假身份证还在吗
Do you still have your fake ID?
{}是啊 我得回家让我妈看看我的厉害
Yeah. I've got to go home and kiss my mother's ass
{}没喝醉我是不会回去的
and I'm not going to do it sober.
{}我可没想知道那么多
... More than I needed to know.
{}他都吓傻了 完全傻了
He was in shock. He was totally shocked.
{}他说 议员 这可是竞选
He said, "Congressman, this was the campaign
{}这张票不算 你已经投过了
This was not the vote. You voted already."
{}-就是这么回事 -真有意思
- That's what it was. - I love that one!
{}这点心看着就好吃
Oh, the desserts look wonderful.
{}勒奈特 要帮忙吗
Lynette, Do you need any help?
{}没事 我能搞定
I got it covered. No problem.
{}斯加沃 该你了 说说你的天才创意
Ok, Scavo. You're up. Let's hear this genius idea of yours.
{}好的
Ok. Uh...
{}好
Ok.
{}现在洁力强面临的最大问题是
The single greatest obstacle facing Spotless Scrub
{}缺少曝光率
is a lack of visibility
{}我们要重点把广告发布在
We need to concentrate ad spending in places
{}女人花时间最多的地方
where women spend the majority of their time.
{}举例说吧 大型连锁超市
For example, large chain grocery stores.
{}把洁力强的广告贴在
Picture spotless scrub ads on the
{}每个妈妈的手推车两侧
side of every mother's shopping cart.
{}-有意思 -其实还有更好的
- Interesting. - Oh, You know what'd be even better?
{}-干洗袋 -什么
- Dry-cleaning bags. - What?
{}真的 听我说
No, Really. Hear me out.
{}把洁力强的大广告放在
Put a big Spotless Scrub ad
{}女人和她的开司米羊绒衫中间
between a woman and her cashmere sweater.
{}我保你能吸引到她们的注意
I gurantee you'll get her attention.
{}亲爱的 主意不错 但我正说到一半
Honey. That's great. I'm I'm in the middle of a thing here.
{}她说得没错 那样我就会注意到的
She's got a point. I would notice that.
{}而且干洗袋会一直挂在我们的衣橱里
And those dry-cleaning bags hang in our closets forever.
{}-就像个永久性广告 -完全正确
- So it is like constant advertising. - Exactly!
{}或许这方法可行 但是
You know, maybe that's the way we can work that in, but...
{}不 这注意妙极了
No, this is kind of a fantastic idea.
{}要在全国实施吗
We go nationwide with this?
{}当然要 从顶尖品牌开始着手
Why not? Start by targeting the top chain.
{}然后延伸出去
Then branch out from there.
{}最后 渗透到整个市场
Boom, boom, boom. Mass saturation.
{}其实 还有个更好的主意
And you know what else would be a great idea?
{}在勒奈特独领风骚的时候
While Lynette was commanding everyone's attention...
{}苏珊却在尽力保持低调
Susan was trying to remain inconspicuous.
{}大家都在看着我 是吧
Everybody's looking at me, aren't they?
{}就是些看热闹的
Just the slapstick fans.
{}天哪 我怎么就没晕过去呢
Oh, god, why couldn't I have just been knocked unconscious?
{}-啤酒 -当然
- Beer? - Absolutely.
{}-苏珊 这是凯德拉 -你介绍过了
- Susan, this is Kendra. - We've been introduced.
{}不 我和凯德拉是老朋友了
No.This is Kendra. We've been friends for years.
{}她只是过来玩玩 明天就走
She's only visit. She's leaving tomorrow
{}-就这样而已 -确实
- That's it. - It's true.
{}我从来没对这男人有什么想法
I have no designs on this man whatsoever.
{}我马上回来
I'll be right back.
{}-抱歉让你误会了 -我也是
- Sorry about the misunderstanding. - Me, too.
{}你们俩开始约会多久啦
So how long have you two been seeing each other?
{}其实第一次就被你打断了
Well, you sort of interrupted our first date.
{}在这之前都是不温不火的
But up until then, smoking-hot tension.
{}听起来没什么希望 我知道
Sounds pathetic, I know.
{}不 我觉得细水长流很好
No, it's good to take it slow.
{}够聪明的话就多加小心
You'd be smart to be careful.
{}-有什么特殊原因吗 -听着
- Any particular reason? - Look...
{}麦克是挺完美的 真的
Mike's a wonderful guy. Really.
{}但是你该问问他为什么会搬到紫藤郡
But you should ask him why he moved to Wisteria Lane.
{}说来话长啊
It's one hell of a story.
{}来 我拿了些冰
Here. Got some ice.
{}-给 -谢谢
- There you go. - Thanks.
{}我过得很开心 谢谢伙计们 再见
Well, it's been fun. Thanks, guys. See you later.
{}-晚上好 -晚上好
- Good evening. - Good evening.
{}坐吧
Have a seat.
{}我得习惯这种告别方式
I could get used to this whole closure thing.
{}我喜欢依依不舍
I love long goodbyes.
{}在转角等我 我马上回来
Wait around the corner. I'll be right back.
{}笑一个 加布丽尔
Smile, Gabrielle.
{}这样也好
Well, that's it, then.
{}你干吗呢 她拍到我们了
What are you doing? She had a camera.
{}我们得抓住她
We've got to catch her.
{}索利斯夫人 你丈夫会杀了我们的
Mrs. Solis, your husband's going to kill us.
{}快啊
Come on!
{}-放开我 -把相机给我
- Leave me alone. - Give me that camera!
{}我没跟你闹着玩 老女人
I'm not kidding, old woman!
{}走开 别碰我
Stay away from me! Don't touch me!
{}别过去
No.
{}别去 你回家吧 我来搞定
No, you go home. I'll take care of this.
{}还有 你从来没到这来过 走吧
And you were never here. Go.
{}快走
Go!
{}你看见了吗 有个人开着车
Did you see that? A guy came barreling
{}拐弯冲过来撞到她然后逃逸了
around the corner and just hit her.
{}-有手机吗 -有
- Do you have a cell phone? - Yeah.
{}打911
Call 911.
{}-发生什么事啦 -她还有呼吸吗
- What happened? - Is she breathing?
{}当胡安妮塔·蒂德战兢着看到那束白光时
As Juanita Tetered dangerously close to the white light,
{}勒奈特和汤姆陷则掉进了无底洞
Lynette and Tom were headed into a black hole.
{}我只不过参与了一下
I was just participating.
{}你的参与该仅限于
Your participation was supposed
{}准备晚饭而已
to be limited to making dinner,
{}而不是贬低我的创意
not making my ideas look bad.
{}可能你需要更好的创意
You konw. Maybe you need better ideas.
{}对不起 我不是那个意思
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I didn't mean that.
{}不 我们都知道 在有孩子们之前
No, we both know that your career
{}你的事业比我的辉煌多了
was going so much better than mine before we had kids.
{}-你不用一直提醒我 -这不公平
- You never let me forget that. - That is not fair.
{}过去你总是和我竞争
You were always competing with me,
{}从今晚的表现看 你还是这样
and judging by tonight, you konw what, still are.
{}汤姆 今晚的事我真的很抱歉
Tom, I am sorry about tonight. Truly.
{}但要说我在和谁竞争的话
But these days if I'm competing with anyone
{}那是布里·范德坎普
it's the Bree Van de Kamps of the world,
{}还有一尘不染的厨房 优秀的孩子们
with their spotless kitchens and their perfect kids,
{}还能不出一点差错办出最棒的派对
who throw fabulous parties where nothing ever goes wrong.
{}我百般努力试图赶上 可我做不到
I try so hard to keep up but I can't.
{}勒奈特 我没期望那些
Lynette. That's not my expectation.
{}每次你接到策划案 邀请合伙人过来
And when you work on a pitch, you bring the parteners over.
{}都会让我想起我放弃的那个世界
I am reminded of a world I left behind,
{}我在那是长胜将军 是大家的目标
where I was the winner and people tried to keep up with me.
{}我既回不到过去 也做不好主妇
I can't go back, I can't win where I am.
{}我现在进退两难
I am stuck in the middle
{}而且这事真的让我
and it's really something that gets me...
{}跟你说
Whoa! For your information,
{}你今天办的晚宴棒极了
I thought you threw an amazing dinner party tonight.
{}简直让我喜出望外
I was thrilled.
{}我不知道你怎么能把这些事联系起来
I don't know how you pulled it all together.
{}-可是 -你信也好不信也好
- Yeah, well... - And whether you believe it or not,
{}每个认识你的人都觉得
everyone who knows you thinks that
{}你是个好妻子 也是个好妈妈
you are a great wife and mother.
{}-他们才没这么想 -他们是这么想的
- No, they don't. - Yes, they do.
{}尤其是我
Especially me.
{}谢谢
Thanks.
{}你眼睛怎么了
What's wrong with your eyes?
{}没事 就是累了
Nothing. I'm tired.
{}-过来让我看看 -我没事 真的
- Turn around. I want to look at you. - I'm fine. Really
{}外面怎么回事
What's going on outside?
{}就那儿
Right there.
{}谢天谢地你们来了
Oh my god. Thank god you're here.
{}去陪陪加布丽尔好吗 我马上过来
Will you take care of Gabrielle? I have to come home for a minute.
{}没问题
All right.
{}安德鲁 你回来太好了
Oh, Andrew. Thank god you're back.
{}我需要你帮忙 亲爱的
I need your help, honey.
{}刚刚发生了场意外
There's been an accident.
{}安德鲁
Andrew?
{}妈妈
Mama?
{}安德鲁
Andrew!
{}雷克斯 你得回家一趟
Rex, you need to come home.
{}发生了些事 我们需要你
Something's happened and we need you.
{}竞争 通常因人而异
Competition. It means different things to different people.
{}但是无论选择和平竞争
But whether it's a friendly rivalry
{}还是生死决斗
or a fight to the death...
{}干杯
Cheers.
{}结局都是一样的
...The end result is the same.
{}总会有胜利者
There will be winners...
{}也会有失败者
and there will be losers.
{}当然 诀窍是
Of course, the trick is...
{}识时务者 纵观全局
to know which battles to fight.
{}不入虎穴 焉得虎子
You see, no victory comes without a price.